<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>ITSecurityGard</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2016-12-15T12:00:00+08:00</updated><entry><title>Application Logic Vulnerability Devfest Codelabs</title><link href="/application-logic-vulnerability-devfest-codelabs.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-12-15T12:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2016-12-15T12:00:00+08:00</updated><author><name>Kent Bayron</name></author><id>tag:,2016-12-15:application-logic-vulnerability-devfest-codelabs.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today i want to share to you the bug i found on devfest codelabs, me and my colleagues decided to joined the codelabs for the first time, we were answering the codelabs that time but suddenly the competition is so strange, the other participants was so shocked because their score is reaching over the actual score, they found first a accidental bug but they didnt know what it is, they didn't know whats happening that time, they were just answering the codelabs and it turns that they were the rank 1 in the ranking, they keep telling that their score is something that doubles up. So I have my very curious brain so i know that there's a vulnerability here. The next thing i do is i keep digging digging and boom i found something , i found logic vuln and i reported it to their devs .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/gdg.PNG" /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if you enjoy this give me a feedback as a comment or drop me an email at kntx501@gmail.com. if you are interested i might do a complete write up about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/gifs/raw1.gif" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="Security"></category><category term="Logic Vulnerability"></category></entry><entry><title>Insecure Direct Object Reference Vulnerability Buksusisonline</title><link href="/insecure-direct-object-reference-vulnerability-buksusisonline.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-12-14T13:37:00+08:00</published><updated>2016-12-14T13:37:00+08:00</updated><author><name>Kent Bayron</name></author><id>tag:,2016-12-14:insecure-direct-object-reference-vulnerability-buksusisonline.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone!
This blog post is about the vulnerabilities i found in buksusisonline. the bug lies in the profile picture feature of buksusisonline which allow anyone to access with just modifying the student number. i also found file path disclosure vulnerability which anyone can view the path of the root file of the site but for now this vuln is consedered as a "noise" or out of scope vuln .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Student Information System Can view Student Profile,Grades, Ledgers
and Available Courses for the current semester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my testing there's an error, a very interesting error and what i did is i keep digging and i found a vulnerability which i can view the path of their files that consedered as a file path disclosure vulnerability:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/pd.png" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also found out that the profile picture parameter is pointing to the student number(object) which is vulnerable to insecure direct object reference. I'm curious about it ,i changed the parameter and boom i can now view the other student using their student ID number. 
&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/idor.png" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm already report this to the admin, thanks to Sir.Dexcleir, 
&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/pr.png" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if you enjoy this give me a feedback as a comment or drop me an email at kntx501@gmail.com. if you are interested i might do a complete write up about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/gifs/raw.gif" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="IDOR"></category><category term="Security"></category></entry><entry><title>XSS-Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability Via Search Bar</title><link href="/xss-cross-site-scripting-vulnerability-via-search-bar.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-12-08T14:37:00+08:00</published><updated>2016-12-08T14:37:00+08:00</updated><author><name>Kent Bayron</name></author><id>tag:,2016-12-08:xss-cross-site-scripting-vulnerability-via-search-bar.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello Readers! 
Today, I will tell you a story about the vuln i found on a online website, this website is a catalog for thier equipments and hardware tools available in thier store. so here is the scenario, i was browsing to their site , looking for some tools and eqiupment that i can use to assess my daily study, I was searching that time and when i hit enter there's something unusual result, the result is only backslash "/". So the first thing that comes up in my mind is this site is vulnerable to XSS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reproduction Steps
&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/write.png" /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Result page will trigger like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/xss.png" /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The image above contains the session cookies of the site and other cookies. I already reported this vulnerability to their Devs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if you enjoy this give me a feedback as a comment or drop me an email at kntx501@gmail.com. if you are interested i might do a complete write up about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/gifs/raw3.gif" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="XSS"></category><category term="Security"></category></entry><entry><title>Data Driven Assesstment (diminishing FTW) via How to Shot Web</title><link href="/data-driven-assesstment-diminishing-ftw-via-how-to-shot-web.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-12-02T11:37:00+08:00</published><updated>2016-12-02T11:37:00+08:00</updated><author><name>Jason Haddix</name></author><id>tag:,2016-12-02:data-driven-assesstment-diminishing-ftw-via-how-to-shot-web.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h6&gt;How to test web app in minutes&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1.Visit the search, registration, contact, password reset, and comment forms and hit them with your polyglot strings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2.Scan those specific functions with Burps built-in scanner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3.Check your cookie, log out, check cookie, log in, check cookie.Submit old cookie, see if access.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4.Perform user enumeration checks on login, registration, and password reset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5.Do a reset and see if; the password comes plaintext, uses a URL based token, is predictable, can be used multiple times, or logs you in automatically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6.Find numeric account identifiers anywhere in URLs and rotate them for context change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7.Find the security-sensitive function(s) or files and see if vulnerable to non-auth browsing (idors), lower-auth browsing, CSRF, CSRF protection bypass, and see if they can be done over HTTP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8.Directory brute for top short list on SecLists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;9.Check upload functions for alternate file types that can execute code (xss or php/etc/etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</summary><category term="Security"></category><category term="Web"></category></entry><entry><title>COMELEAK Hack 2016</title><link href="/comeleak-hack-2016.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-11-30T16:37:00+08:00</published><updated>2016-11-30T16:37:00+08:00</updated><author><name>Kent Bayron</name></author><id>tag:,2016-11-30:comeleak-hack-2016.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h6&gt;March 27, 2016&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A group of hacktivist widely known as "Anonymous", Anonymous Philippines claimed that they defaced the comelec website.
They gain access to the root path with the root privileges by using power and appers to be an XPath injection Vuln. Anonymous Philippines request the implementation of the security features of the PCOS machines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hours later, The leaks has been copied. The data appears to personal informations containing names, Precint numbers and Voters identification numbers. The good thing is data is encrpted but the decryption keys were leaked. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Alt Text" src="/images/lek.png" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comelec doesn’t seems to take serious security measures, even displaying sensitive info in plain text!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;April 20, 2016&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The suspect was arrested in his house in Sampaloc, Manila &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Defacing the Comelec Website was meant "TO GIVE VOICE TO THE VOICELESS" Paul Biteng told the Inquirer in an interview. But the data leak was not part of the plan, He added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sources:
&lt;a href="Http://www.technology.inquirer.net/47763/boredom-made-me-do-it-says-comelec-hacker"&gt;www.technology.inquirer.net&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href="www.interaksyon.com/infotech/entire-comelec-database-available-via-torrent-malacananf-seeding-it"&gt;www.interaksyon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="Security"></category><category term="Web"></category><category term="Data-Breach"></category></entry><entry><title>Clifford Trigo Bug Bounty Wannabe</title><link href="/clifford-trigo-bug-bounty-wannabe.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-11-16T07:37:00+08:00</published><updated>2016-11-16T07:37:00+08:00</updated><author><name>Kent Bayron</name></author><id>tag:,2016-11-16:clifford-trigo-bug-bounty-wannabe.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A friend of mine, He is Clifford Trigo, He is a security researcher that focuses on web applications and services from Bohol, Philippines. Currently, He is listed in Hackerone’s top 10 list of hackers overall. In connection, He is also the top 1 in Square’s and Yelp’s (private) bug bounty programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Security is what i love and bug bounties open the possibility of doing security work, in my case into web applications, without the possibility of getting jailed and also making the web more secure. one bug might take hours to find, but every single bug is thrilling to look for, in addition, bug bounty equals profit. Considering the exchange rate from bounties paid in USD to Philippine Peso" He added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="hackerone.com/Thanks"&gt;hackerone.com/Thanks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="hackerone.com/Square (square.com)"&gt;hackerone.com/Square (square.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="hackerone.com/Yelp (yelp.com)"&gt;hackerone.com/Yelp (yelp.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="hackerone.com/BookFresh (bookfresh.com)"&gt;hackerone.com/BookFresh (bookfresh.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackerone.com/Irccloud (irccloud.com)"&gt;https://hackerone.com/Irccloud (irccloud.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://ph.linkedin.com/pub/clifford-trigo/a8/a57/73b"&gt;https://ph.linkedin.com/pub/clifford-trigo/a8/a57/73b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</summary><category term="Security"></category><category term="Web"></category><category term="Data-Breach"></category><category term="Bug Hunter"></category></entry></feed>